下面是臭味代码的第三个例子
Here's the third example of smelly code
这将说明剩下的
that's going to illustrate the remaining
阅读要点。
points of this reading.
所以Count Log Words是一个获取字符串列表的函数，
So Count Log Words is a function that takes a list of strings,
它将要做什么
and what its going to do it's going
数数单词的数目
to count the number of words, the number
列表中的字符串
of strings in that list, that are
超过一定长度的。
longer than a certain length.
这个长度是由这个长字长的名字给出的。
And that length is given by this long word length name here.
它会跟踪变量n中的计数。
And it's going to keep track of that count in this variable n.
然后它也会跟踪
And then it's also going to keep track
最长的单词是什么。
of what the longest word is.
每当它找到一个比当前最长的词
Whenever it finds a word that's longer than the current longest
单词，它会记住最长的单词
word, it's going to remember that in it's longest word
变量。
variable.
它会打印到系统输出
And it's going to print to System Out, which
只是控制台，它找到的长单词数。
is just the console, the number of long words to that it found.
这段代码有几个问题。
There's a couple of things wrong with this code.
其中之一是它使用全局变量。
One of them is that it uses global variables.
这里有两个，长单词长度最长的单词。
There's two of them here, long word length the longest word.
我们知道它们是全球性的
And the way that we know that they're global
是因为他们面前有公众这个词
is that they have the word public in front of them, which
意味着可以在代码中的任何地方访问它们。
means they can be accessed anywhere in the code.
他们面前有“静”这个词，
They have the word static in front of them,
这意味着它们与物体无关，
which means that they're not associated with an object,
但实际上——这只是一个变量
but are instead-- this is just one single variable
表示此值。
representing this value.
最后，我们知道它们是变量，
And finally, we know that they're variables,
他们可以改变因为他们没有
that they can change because they don't have
属性final在这里，我们讨论过
the attribute final in here, which we talked
在先前的阅读中。
about in an earlier reading.
所以当你有一个变量和全局的东西时，
So any time you have a thing that is variable and global,
你在为自己冒险。
you're making risks for yourself.
这个网页的全局变量是坏的
And this web page Global Variables Are Bad
很好地总结了许多原因
has a nice summary of many of the reasons
为什么全局变量对于良好的编程是危险的。
why global variables are dangerous for good programming.
在Java中，可以检测全局变量
In Java you can detect a global variable
注意到它被宣布为公共静电，
by noticing that it is declared as public static,
也没有决赛。
and it doesn't have a final.
公共修饰符使它可以在任何地方访问，
A public modifier makes it accessible anywhere,
静态意味着它与一个对象没有关联。
and the static means that it's not associated with an object.
一般来说，你想去掉这些全局变量，
Generally, you want to get rid of these global variables,
所以在这种情况下，最长的单词是一个全局变量
so in this case longest word is a global variable
因为那是它储存一个结果的地方。
because that's where it's storing one of its results.
但你真的应该把这个结果还给我。
But you should really return this result.
你应该想办法，而不是储存东西
You should find a way, instead of storing things
在一个全局变量中，供代码的其余部分访问，
in a global variable for the rest of your code to access,
相反，您应该将内容作为参数传递
you should instead be passing things as parameters
并将它们作为返回值返回。
and returning them as return values.
我们将在未来看到许多这样做的技术。
And we'll see many techniques for doing that in the future.
还有一件事，这看起来很小，但是很多人
Another thing-- and this may seem minor but many people
一开始犯这样的错误
make mistakes like this at first-- is
当你写方法的时候，
that when you're writing a method,
考虑让它返回结果
think about having it return its results
而不是把它们打印出来放在控制台上。
rather than print them out to the console for human eyeballs.
如果你把东西打印出来，那么你写的代码
If you're printing things out, then the code your writing
还没准备好改变。
isn't really ready for change.
它还没有准备好在其他上下文中重用。
It isn't ready for reuse in some other context.
这是打印它的计数，而不是返回它。
This is printing its count instead of returning it.
一般来说，只有程序的最高级别部分
In general, only the highest level parts your program
应该与人类用户交互
should interact with the human user
或者把东西打印到控制台上。
or print things out to the console.
可以打印调试信息
It's OK to print debugging information
当你开发它的时候，但是那个窃听器
while you're developing it, but that bugging
信息不应该是你设计的一部分。
information shouldn't be a part of your design.
它不应该是功能的一部分
It shouldn't be a part of how the function is
应该有用的。
supposed to work.
它应该只是调试设计的一部分。
It should only be a part of how you debug your design.